paradisenutrition.in 2018-08-29

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy - Your Privacy Rights**

**Privacy Policy Effective Date: 01,OCTOBER 2015**

At Paradise Nutrition Inc. we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, and therefore do not sell or rent our customers’ Personal Information to any third party. Further, we do not share your Personal Information with any third parties for their direct marketing purposes without first providing you the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of such sharing. You may request information about how we share information consistent with this Privacy Policy by contacting us at: info@[paradisenutrition.in](mailto:info@sannindia.net)

The www.paradisenutrition.in are owned by Paradise Nutrition Inc. We refer to Paradise Nutrition Inc. as the “ **Company** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ” or “ **our**.”

This page sets forth our policies regarding the use and disclosure of information we collect from or are able to obtain about the Sites’ users. We refer to these policies as our “ **Privacy Policy**.” In addition to the lower case words “we,” “us” and “our” defined above, you will notice that we capitalize certain words in this Privacy Policy even though the rules of grammar do not require that they be capitalized. We do this because these words have specific meanings in this Privacy Policy. These specific meanings are found where the capitalized words are placed in bold text and inside quotation marks.

We hope this Privacy Policy will answer your questions regarding how we treat information gathered from our Sites. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, other than requests for our information sharing practices as described in the first paragraph above, please feel free to contact us at info@[paradisenutrition.in](mailto:info@sannindia.net) or, if you wish to exclude your Personal Information from our direct marketing programs including e-mail, please refer to the section titled “How to Opt-Out,” below.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide to us, or that we may obtain through means other than the Sites, such as by phone or postal mail, but please note that Personal Information obtained through such means will be treated in accordance with the first paragraph above and our use of such Personal Information will be consistent with this Privacy Policy. By accessing and using the Sites you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use the Sites. Furthermore, by providing us with Personal Information on the Sites, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

As we update and diversify our products and services, this Privacy Policy may change. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check this page for updates periodically. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here. Unless the law otherwise requires, we do not provide notice of changes to this Privacy Policy and your use of the Sites following any posted changes will indicate your acceptance of such changes.

**What Information We Collect and Inactively Gather?**

**Personal Information**

In order to process orders efficiently, when you place an order with us or register an account on the Sites we actively collect the following personal information: name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address and phone number, (“ **Personal Information** ”). If you prefer not to disclose your Personal Information online, you can always place your order by visiting one of the many stores where our products are sold.

We may periodically conduct surveys of visitors to our Sites for internal research purposes that may include marketing. This helps us better understand what our customers would like to see from us. If you respond to such surveys, we may ask you for some Personal Information and/or may contact you for more information, but only if you have given us permission to do so.

We may also receive information about you from other sources.

**Usage Information**

We (including through our third party service providers) may inactively collect from you information that is not in the same category as Personal Information. For example, we might track information about the date and time you access the Sites, the type of web browser you used, and the websites from which you connect to our Sites. We collect and use this and other non-Personal Information (such as demographic data) to analyze and develop our business strategy and to determine how you found out about us, your interests regarding our products and services and how to further improve our Sites. We, or a third party, may also collect information from your activities on the Sites for the purposes of providing advertisements and other content to you at the Sites that are customized to your interests and preferences. To accomplish all this, and also to allow us to offer our customers streamlined ordering and other useful features, we, as do many websites, use the technologies listed below and other similar technologies (the “ **Tracking Technologies** ”):

  * **Cookies and Clear GIFs** \- Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies make web surfing easier for you by saving your customer identification information (i.e. username, password, shopping cart information, etc.) while you’re at our Sites. Cookies also track where you travel on our Sites and what you look at and purchase. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a web page or message.
  * **IP Address Tracking and Clickstream Data** \- In addition to cookies and clear GIFs, our servers automatically collect data about your server’s Internet address when you visit our Sites. This information, known as an Internet Protocol Address, or “ **IP Address** ”, is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you are on the Internet. When you view pages from our Sites, our servers may record or “log” your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server also may record the page that linked you to us and related information including any ads you may have clicked on. Such information is known as “ **Clickstream Data** ”.
  * **Email Interconnectivity** \- If you receive email from us, we may use certain tools to capture data related to when you open our message, click on any links or banners it contains and make purchases.

In some cases, we may link the non-Personal Information collected through the Tracking Technologies with certain of your Personal Information. WE WANT TO BE SURE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THAT ACCEPTING TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES ONTO YOUR COMPUTER IN NO WAY GIVES US ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER OR ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU. YOU MAY SET YOUR WEB BROWSER SOFTWARE TO REJECT TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES, BUT, IF YOU DO SO, CERTAIN FUNCTIONALITY OF THE SITES MAY BE AFFECTED. Third parties (including, but not limited to, software vendors, advertisers and fulfillment companies) may also use Tracking Technologies by or through the Sites. WE HAVE NO CONTROL OVER WHAT INFORMATION SUCH THIRD PARTIES TRACK OR COLLECT, AND HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY TRACKING, DATA COLLECTION OR OTHER ACTIVITIES OF SUCH THIRD PARTIES.

**Security of the Information You Provide**

Among our top priorities is keeping your Personal Information secure. The computers that store your Personal Information may be located in a separate facility which employs security technology. We employ these procedures to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

You may be able to create an account on our Sites with a username and password, including if you set up a customer account. We recommend you exercise extreme care in protecting your password information and do not publicly share any of your passwords. You are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of the Sites by you or another person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you.

Your Personal Information will be stored and processed on our computers in the India. The laws on holding Personal Information in India may vary and be less stringent than laws of your state or country. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to hold and transmit your Personal Information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. If you object to your Personal Information being transferred or used in this manner please do not register with or use the Sites.

ALTHOUGH WE WILL TAKE (AND REQUIRE OUR THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS TO TAKE) REASONABLE SECURITY PRECAUTIONS TO PROTECT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM AND STORED ON THE SITES, BECAUSE OF THE OPEN NATURE OF THE INTERNET, WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT PERSONAL INFORMATION STORED ON OUR SERVERS, TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM A USER, OR OTHERWISE IN OUR CARE WILL BE ABSOLUTELY SAFE FROM INTRUSION BY OTHERS, SUCH AS HACKERS. ACCORDINGLY, WE DISCLAIM ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY THEFT OR LOSS OF, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR DAMAGE TO, OR INTERCEPTION OF ANY DATA OR COMMUNICATIONS. BY USING THE SITES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO ASSUME THESE RISKS.

**How Do We Use the Information that You Provide and We Collect?**

We collect Personal Information for the purposes of fulfilling orders and providing you with the services you have chosen, providing a high level of customer service, providing you with information we believe may be of interest including mailing our newsletter, circulars and special offers, for editorial and feedback purposes, for internal marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of your behavior, for product development, for content improvement and to customize the content and layout of the Sites (collectively, “ **Information Usage Purposes** ”). In performing the Information Usage Purposes, we may combine information we collect on the Sites with information we receive from other sources. We do not sell Personal Information and we do not disclose Personal Information to any other party, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, any non-Personal Information you transmit to the Sites or we collect from the Sites will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary and you agree that we may use any such non-Personal Information (together with any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained therein) in any manner, for any purpose, without credit or compensation to you.

**Sharing of Your Information With Our Partners; Transfer of Your Information**

We may provide your Personal Information to our associates and to companies acting as our authorized agents or partners in providing our service or co-branded services to you and in performing Information Usage Purposes. We screen and reasonably determine to be reputable any third party to whom we disclose such information and we require such third parties to agree to use the Personal Information only for such specified purposes. Each of our partners must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of your Personal Information in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

If we merge, or sell or otherwise transfer our assets, Sites or operations, we may disclose or transfer your Personal Information in connection with such transaction.

**How to Opt-out**

We will be sending e-mail for customer service purposes and various offers and/or circulars.

If at any time you wish to stop receiving offers and/or circulars e-mail from us, you can always remove your name from our mailing list by sending an e-mail to info@[paradisenutrition.in](mailto:info@sannindia.net)   stating that you wish to unsubscribe and indicating in the subject line of the e-mail "NO E-MAIL". Although we will promptly remove your name from our offers and newsletter e-mail list upon receiving your request, it is possible that you may still receive e-mails from us that had been initiated prior to your name being removed from our list. You can also contact us by mail:

Paradise Nutrition Inc.  
Attention:  Customer Service - Privacy  
Internet Division  
62, Bajaj Bhawan, 226 Nariman Point,   
Mumbai 400 021. India  
info@[paradisenutrition.in](mailto:info@sannindia.net)

THE OPT-OUT RIGHTS AND PROCEDURES DESCRIBED IN THIS SECTION ARE THE DEFAULT RULES AND PROCEDURES WE USE IN OPERATING THE SITES AND ARE THE STANDARD BY WHICH WE ADHERE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.

**Release of Information to Protect Our Sites and Others**

We may release Personal Information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is necessary to comply with law, protect the rights, properties or safety of the Company, our users or others, or enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements.

**Your Account Access Rights**

You may review and make changes to the Personal Information that is stored in your user account on the Sites by visiting the “My Account” area of the Sites.

**Intended Users; Use by Children under 13**

**The Sites is not purposefully directed at children under the age of 13 and** **all products available for sale on the Sites are intended to be purchased by adults.** We do not collect or maintain Personal Information, via the Sites or otherwise, from those we actually know are children under 13 years of age. If you notify us that information has been provided by a child under the age of 13, upon verification, we will promptly delete such information.

**Third Party Ad Servers; Links to Other Websites**

We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Sites. The Sites also may contain links to other websites that are not under our control. These links may include the use of so-called “share links.” A “share link” is a button and/or text link appearing on our Sites that enables the launch of a sharing mechanism whereby you can post links to, and content from, the Sites onto social networking websites such as Facebook. The privacy policies of other website operators or advertisers may significantly differ from our Privacy Policy. We urge you to read the privacy statements of each and every website you visit and to contact the third party website operators or advertisers directly if you have any questions or concerns about their data collection or privacy policies. WE HAVE NO CONTROL OR INFLUENCE OVER THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF SUCH OTHER WEBSITES AND ADVERTISERS AND WE DO NOT ASSUME ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY THIRD PARTY WEBSITE OPERATORS’ OR ADVERTISERS’ DATA COLLECTION PRACTICES, THEIR FAILURE TO ABIDE BY THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES OR THE CONTENT OF ANY THIRD PARTY WEBSITE.

 |    
---|---  
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |    
  |
